Morning!
Inaba...
Sorry!
I shouldn't have yelled at you!
Kiriyama was hurting, so
I was focused on her.
And since I had an episode right then...
I'm disappointed, Inaba.
I never thought you would
give up on your friends.
Well, you couldn't help it.
Yes, I could have.
I know how hard it is for you, and yet...
I'm not upset.
You only said those things because
you were worried about Yui.
But don't ask me to go to the
clubroom or Yui's house just yet.
I need some time.
I believe you belong with us!
Let me know if you need help!
And I hope you come back soon.
It feels like we're losing people.
I'm thinking that she's more upset
about what she said to Yui than about
what Taichi said to her.
Inaban's a lot more
sensitive than she looks.
Should we leave her alone for now?
I'm worried about Yui, too.
Is she going to have attendance issues?
It's only been a week.
I don't think that's a concern yet.
But if she keeps this up...
It's getting lonely.
Inaba will be back once she's
had a little time alone.
Let's focus on Kiriyama right now.
But Yui doesn't want to see us.
Yesterday...
Her mom would have let us
in if she were around.
But what are we supposed to do
after we've managed to
get inside her room?
We have to go see her before
we can do anything.
Kiriyama might be feeling better today.
But what if one of us
has an episode and makes
the situation worse again?
Er, didn't we already
go over this yesterday?
What do we do?
It's not our decision to make.
I can understand Yui's reasoning,
but if she keeps it up,
Heartseed might try something.
I believe the current situation
is bad for Kiriyama.
But if Yui goes outside,
it'll only get worse.
She might end up physically
harming other people.
Though we have the same problem.
But Kiriyama looks so sad.
You're only worried about dealing
with Yui's current problem!
You need to think ahead!
Our first priority should be to deal
with Kiriyama's current problem!
Because of that "must help everyone
immediately" mentality you're so good at?
You think your selfless behavior
will save the day again?
What's that supposed to mean?
Don't you want to help Kiriyama?!
Wait... Taichi? Aoki?
I want to help her,
but I don't know what to do!
Then we should start by
going to see Kiriyama!
What do we do after that?!
We find a way!
We couldn't find a way
the past two days!
We won't change anything by
standing around talking!
That doesn't mean we should
keep trying the same thing!
Cut it out, guys!
Calm down, Aoki!
Forget it.
I'll go by myself.
What?
Don't just decide these things yourself!
Today, I'm doing things my way.
I can save Kiriyama.
Who do you think you are?!
Do you seriously believe
you can save everyone?!
Isn't that what happened when
we were swapping personalities?
You were no help at all!
Calm down, Aoki!
You too, Taichi!
You can't get lucky every time!
Are you trying to hog
all the glory again?!
Hog all the glory?!
I'm going to save Kiriyama!
Save her?!
You're just a selfish freak who doesn't
want to see Yui look sad!
Shut up!
At least I'm not a worthless
clod who can't do jack!
What was that?
I told you guys to cut it out!
Taichi, you're getting to
be too full of yourself!
Aoki, you're getting too jealous!
Are either of you actually
worried about Yui?!
You guys just don't want
to see Yui looking sad!
Don't interfere!
Outta my way!
A-Are you okay, Nagase?!
See?!
You're a selfish bastard who
doesn't care if anyone
is hurt in the process!
Er...
I didn't mean that.
Sorry.
Don't blame yourself.
Your desires were unleashed, that's all.
It wasn't your fault.
My desires were unleashed
when I shoved Nagase.
But...
They weren't before then.
The episode didn't begin until...
Don't interfere!
Even without my desires
being unleashed, I...
Big brother?
What's wrong? Why are the lights off?
Are you asleep?
No, you need something?
You haven't come out of your room,
so I was wondering if you were sick.
Do you have a cold?
It's nothing.
You should probably stay
away from me right now.
Did you get in a fight
with your girlfriend?
Huh?
Oh, I guessed right.
That's no good.
Boys are stronger, so they're
supposed to protect girls.
You're absolutely right.
You should make up right away.
Bye.
Even my little sister
is worried about me.
What am I doing?
I see...
Is this how Kiriyama feels?
Oh, Mom?
Ah, you're seeing him again tonight?
Nah, I'll be fine by myself.
No problem at all.
Should I even be here?
What if I have another episode
and do something worse this time?
Stop thinking.
Focus on studying.
Don't think.
Morning, Taichi.
Yeah.
Ao—
Taichi!
You're heading to the clubroom, right?
Huh?
Oh...
You're coming, right?
Oh, Inaban!
Are you coming to the clubroom?
Sorry, I'll have to pass again today.
Bye.
I'm heading home for the day, too.
Sorry.
Hey, is there something
going on with you guys?
No, we're always like this.
Well, I won't deny that
you're always spacing out.
Kiriyama, I think? From Class 1?
She still hasn't come back to school.
Sounds like it.
I don't mean to pry, but are
you guys having issues?
It's nothing like that.
If you say so.
On Friday, there will be
a field trip for everyone in our grade.
Today, we will be assigning groups
and reviewing the itinerary.
What a drag.
It's going to end up more like a picnic.
And where did Mr. Go go?
Isn't it a little irresponsible
for a teacher to let
a student handle everything?
Yeah...
But luckily, we have Queen Fujishima.
She's so beautiful.
Wait...
You're a fan of hers?
Are you a masochist?
First, I want to assign groups
for the main event, making curry.
We'll have six groups.
Five people per group.
And we'll be sharing the facilities
with the other classes.
That's too many groups.
Why can't we have more people?
How could you even suggest such a thing?
It would certainly be fun
to spend this one page of your youth
fooling around with your friends.
But there's something more important
you could be doing instead.
Yes, that would be...
Love!
Limiting the number of members
in each group forces
everyone to work together.
A natural opportunity to cooperate,
for hearts to bond, for skin to touch!
Yet you suggest that we discard
this golden chance?!
Let's try this again.
Go with six groups of five people?
Or do you still want bigger groups?
Six groups please!
We want six groups, Fujishima-neesan!
Very well.
Start by forming small groups
of two to three boys or girls apiece.
If all parties are in
agreement, feel free to
complete your group now.
Begin!
Let's team up, Yaegashi.
Sure, that's fine with me.
And we must include Fujishima-san
as one of our girls!
Er, uh...
I know you want to join
up with Nagase and Inaba,
but I won't let that happen!
You get to have your fun
during club activities,
so help me out this once!
I don't get to have any fun.
And I'm pretty sure that you
can't handle Fujishima.
That's the point!
And why do you act like you know
everything about Fujishima-san?!
S-Stuff happened.
We should stick together, Inaban.
Just in case something happens.
Get away from me.
Don't make me repeat myself.
Y-You don't have to be so harsh!
This is for your own good.
I'm trying to help you!
My opinion is the correct one.
How can you be so sure?!
Hey, Yaegashi...
Don't throw a hissy fit, idiot.
Did you call me an idiot?
Did you just call me an idiot?
Calm down!
Don't you understand?!
Get away from me already.
I'll go wash my face.
Nagase!
Inaba-san...
and Nagase-san get to be in my group.
What are you trying to pull here?
I want you and Nagase-san to get along.
Otherwise, you'll ruin the
experience for the entire class.
You don't have the right
to order us around!
The class representative is
obligated to uphold love
and peace in the class.
That doesn't give you the
right to boss us around!
It does.
Because...
I am the class representative!
Wow! I never knew she was fighting
for her classmates' love!
Are you satisfied, Yaegashi-kun?
Me?!
Are you in a group with Watase-kun?
Then me, Nagase-san, Inaba-san, you,
and Watase-kun will be one group.
Okay?
Wh-Why are you asking me?!
Don't just decide that!
Shut up!
No objections!
I think that's a great group!
That settles it.
Any other groups have
five people already?
Yaegashi, I'll buy you a Coke!
Two, even!
Inaban!
I'll be waiting for you in the clubroom.
Is it Heartseed?!
Oh, Yaegashi!
What are you doing in the
classroom by yourself?
Er, nothing.
Hear me out!
Some of the other teachers
were complaining that this
lectern rattles too much,
so I asked for a better one
and they told me to grab one myself.
Is it the job of a teacher to do that?
They're kept in the storehouse.
But that's so far away.
Yeah, I'm so glad you
were there, Yaegashi.
Well, I didn't have anything else to do.
It would have really sucked
to carry this by myself.
Yikes.
We'll have to do some cleaning up first.
Say...
Are you feeling depressed?
No, not really.
If you want to convince
me, drop the long face.
I know.
You must have been rejected.
Was it Nagase? Inaba?
Or was it Kiriyama?
No, you've got it wrong.
This is when you should
talk to a friend.
Huh?
I'm telling you to talk to a friend.
Oh, don't ask me for any advice.
I know nothing about
high school romance.
But you'll discover that
problems have a way
of working themselves out
if you talk to your friends.
But my friends may get
hurt in the process.
So?
Isn't hurting and troubling each other
just what friends are for?
Oh, I know.
We're talking a love triangle.
I get it now.
But it's better to talk things through
instead of dodging the issue.
If you talk to your
friends face-to-face,
everything will work out.
It might still fail sometimes,
but if you don't talk,
you'll regret it for
the rest of your life.
Wouldn't you rather try and fail?
I suppose...
You can't become true friends
until you've experienced enough conflict.
If you always play it
safe, you'll end up
losing the things that truly matter.
Hey, I actually sound like a teacher!
Were you impressed? Eh?
I might have been impressed if
you hadn't said that last part.
Oh, Fujishima.
Did you have a meeting
for the field trip?
Thanks for the hard work.
Perfect timing.
Can you help Yaegashi out real quick?
Huh?
What?
I just explained to Yaegashi
how it's important to talk to friends.
So can you hear him out?
It sounds like he's got issues.
Yaegashi-kun is no friend of mine.
He's my rival.
What?!
What exactly is your relationship?
So?
Uh, I'm not sure where to start.
What would you do
if talking to someone might hurt them?
Then don't talk to them?
But I have to talk to that person
to make something happen.
Then talk to them?
Uh, but I might hurt
them in the process.
Let me ask you this, Yaegashi-kun.
What's more important to you?
Not hurting that person?
Or talking to that person and
making something happen?
What is it that you truly care about?
Have you considered that?
If you have resolve,
conviction, and a firm grasp
on what's important to you,
everything else just kinda flows.
If you don't know what's
important, you won't know
what to do half the time.
And by the way,
I've always thought that humans
are supposed to hurt each other.
But you're entitled to your
own opinion on that subject.
Sorry.
It's me.
Oh, what's up?
So you need romantic advice?
I've got you covered.
Any other questions?
Nah, you should probably get going.
Let me know if you need anything.
I'm willing to help with anything
that might affect our class.
Who are you, Fujishima?
Me?
Yes, let's see...
You can call me a missionary of love.
Everyone is worried about us.
Up until now, I was only
focused on the StuCS members,
but the five of us aren't
alone in this world.
That should have been obvious.
Nagase!
That's not fair, Taichi.
Doesn't it scream adolescence when you
see two guys having a talk out here?
If you don't mind, can
I stay by your side?
Is the atmosphere you shared
what you care about the most?
How can you say that?!
Shut up!